So ayun, Happy birthday Cherry, Yuri.
So I wanted to make something a little different from your birthday, so here is a website no.
Nandyan 'yung mga memories na kasama ka, alinman, nandyan.
Pero I hope this here brings you more reason to smile, more opportunity to chase your dreams...
and hope more moments you'll be in front.
Nakikita ko naman sayo na natutupad na yung mga pangarap mo.
And maybe someday, I see you in the television, o cinema, sana.
Sana man! Sana. I'm going to watch it. Promise.
So again, I'm happy to see how far you come and I always be rooting for your success.
So yun, enjoy your special day. You deserve all the happiness and blessing coming your way.
And that's all. Happy birthday Cherry, Yuri. Send it to you.